Yusheng
魚生
if you can't eat
如果你不能吃饭
Or I'll make you sushi.
或者我给你做寿司。
Can I use your arm?
我可以用你的手臂吗？
piece of cake
小问题
I'm going to the hospital today
我今天要去医院
see someone
看到某人
looks like you
看起来像你
I was originally today
我本来今天
I'm going to the hospital too.
我也要去医院。
is that so
是这样吗
go to see friends
去看朋友
Why don't you go?
你为什么不去？
died
死了
Deep condolences to you
向您致以沉痛哀悼
It has passed
已经过去了
I won't say it anymore
我不会再说了
Where is your brother?
你弟弟呢？
Has the problem been solved.
问题解决了吗。
I tried my best
我尽力了
Can it be solved?
能解决吗？
Just depends on luck
就看运气吧
some things
有些事情
we have no control
我们无法控制
a bit troublesome
有点麻烦
Like falling dominoes
就像倒下的多米诺骨牌
1 person fell
1人摔倒
a series of reactions occur
发生一系列反应
It seems that this is the trouble you have encountered recently
看来是你最近遇到的麻烦
so many
好多啊
I agree
我同意
if i lose my job
如果我失业了
How about working part-time here?
在这里兼职怎么样？
Understood
明白了
what can I do?
我能做些什么？
Lobby
大堂
you really can't work
你真的不能工作
follow me
跟我来
smile at each other
彼此微笑面对
not suitable for you
不适合你
What do you think I can do?
你觉得我能做什么？
be you
成为你
this may be the best job
这可能是最好的工作
Logically speaking
按理说
I don't like the way it's done
我不喜欢它的完成方式
Change company
换公司
please continue my daily work
请继续我的日常工作
I've been doing this for years
我已经这样做很多年了
There are also certain resources
还有一定的资源
Don't change jobs easily
不要轻易换工作
outside world
外面的世界
Maybe it's just superficial greatness
可能只是表面上的伟大
But my current job is
但我现在的工作是
i don't deserve it
我不值得
Things that have lost their value to you
对你来说已经失去价值的东西
in the eyes of others
在别人眼里
it might be worth it
这可能是值得的
is that so
是这样吗
certainly
当然
it's in your eyes
它在你的眼里
Am I worthy?
我值得吗？
you are with me
你和我在一起
cannot be measured by value
无法用价值来衡量
You are me in Jinhai
你就是津海的我
Important person
重要的人
taste
品尝
I suddenly lost my appetite
我突然没了胃口
how
如何
Which word is mine?
哪个词是我的？
inspired you
启发了你
I'm not that weak
我还没那么弱
Brother's troubles
兄弟的烦恼
not yet resolved
尚未解决
I still need to deal with
我还需要处理
Believe me
相信我
his troubles will be solved
他的麻烦将会得到解决
This is also a woman’s intuition
这也是女人的直觉
Sorry for your food
对不起你的美食
Have the opportunity
有机会
show me your true self
向我展示你的真实自我
Tianyang Brothers
天阳兄弟
Why did you come back?
你为什么回来？
I'm so anxious
我急得要死
I'm having a little trouble
我遇到了一点麻烦
that person
那个人
Is it dead?
它死了吗？
died
死了
Do they doubt us?
他们怀疑我们吗？
I can't pay that much attention
我无法关注那么多
Let’s go rescue Huang Zichen first.
我们先去救黄子晨吧。
call
称呼
work has been done
工作已经完成
I already know
我已经知道了
I would like to thank Manager Taka for his sincerity.
我要感谢Taka经理的诚意。
let me know
让我知道
When can Zicheng come back?
子成什么时候能回来？
I think it will come soon
我想它很快就会到来
Would you like something to drink?
您想喝点什么吗？
Thanks.
谢谢。
when this work is completed
当这项工作完成时
I can't look back
我无法回头
Night fog persists
夜雾持续
Demand more from us
对我们提出更多要求
I know
我知道
Next
下一个
like we fall
就像我们跌倒一样
falling dominoes
倒下的多米诺骨牌
Go together
一起走
No chance to hit the brakes
没有机会踩刹车
Thanks.
谢谢。
no matter what comes next
无论接下来是什么
Things are unpredictable
世事难料
be prepared
做好准备
I know
我知道
Next step
下一步
what are you going to do
你会怎样做
Let’s wait until Huang Zicheng is safe.
等黄子成安全了再说吧。
if you listen to me
如果你听我说
I think of a way to protect you
我想一个办法来保护你
if i'm okay
如果我没事的话
How are you
你还好吗
Thank you, Brother Tianyang
谢谢天阳哥哥
I have one more condition
我还有一个条件
you
你
Don't give up Huang Zichen
不要放弃黄子晨
continue to participate
继续参与
I know
我知道
I want to sever ties with him
我要和他断绝关系
All contacts
所有联系人
Do you think you can do it yourself?
你认为你可以自己做吗？
must
必须
if it's not my fault
如果不是我的错
Neither can he
他也不能
just like now
就像现在一样
They have been in the past few days
他们在过去的几天里
Can let people go
可以让人走
Leave the next thing to me
接下来的事交给我
as necessary
如所须
We will contact you
我们将与您联系
OK
好的
pull him up
把他拉起来
Inject him
给他注射
don't let me die
别让我死
OK
好的
you are a lucky boy
你是个幸运的男孩
can someone help
有人可以帮忙
woke up
醒了
What have they done for me?
他们为我做了什么？
stabilizer
稳定剂
They are looking for you after all
他们毕竟在找你
You are in a good situation.
你的情况很好。
Yao Yao sent
姚姚 发送
elder brother
哥哥
Welcome back
欢迎回来
Have you eaten yet?
你吃过了吗？
I haven't eaten it yet
我还没吃过
I haven't eaten yet. I'll go make you some.
我还没吃呢，我去给你做点吧。
you
你
Don't be too emotional
不要太情绪化
It's Yaoyao
是瑶瑶
I think you're exposed
我认为你暴露了
sooner or later
迟早
I just didn't expect it to be so early
我只是没想到会这么早
But why would she do this?
但她为什么要这么做呢？
spies may become suspicious
间谍可能会起疑心
your identity
你的身份
Exposure is not necessarily a bad thing
暴露不一定是坏事
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
when they have questions
当他们有疑问时
You can cheat this time
这次你可以作弊了
But next time I won't be able to hide it anymore
但下次我就无法再隐藏了
Better yet, tell them
更好的是，告诉他们
find your identity
找到你的身份
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Give me
给我
send you away
把你送走
I'm not kidding
我不是在开玩笑
When did you do this?
你什么时候这么做的？
I'm kidding
我在开玩笑
You want them to come to you.
你希望他们来找你。
if my identity is revealed
如果我的身份被揭露
this is for them
这是为了他们
you have no value
你没有价值
you
你
Apart from
除了
They're using me to blackmail you.
他们利用我来敲诈你
Yes
是的
How are you
你还好吗
Of course I have ways to deal with them.
我当然有办法对付他们。
listen to me
听我说
Don't be impulsive when in danger
遇到危险时不要冲动
protect yourself
保护你自己
don't do anything else
不要做任何其他事情
Although I'm a little dissatisfied
虽然我有点不满意
but this time
但这一次
I made you do the right thing
我让你做了正确的事
I told you
我告诉你了
Don’t be impulsive when encountering danger
遇到危险时切忌冲动
why are you rebellious
你为什么叛逆
This is my desire for life
这是我对生活的渴望
Tony is a suspicious person.
托尼就是一个多疑的人。
if i'm quiet
如果我安静
elusive
难以捉摸
He must be doubting me
他一定是在怀疑我
It tastes like it's been submerged in sea water.
尝起来就像浸在海水里一样。
it's painful
很痛苦
I am very smart myself
我自己很聪明
What is it used for?
它是做什么用的？
let us do something for them
让我们为他们做点什么吧
What
什么
Did not say
不说
Confidentiality maintained
機密保持
I don't listen
我不听
they promised me
他们答应我
I won't bother you anymore
我不会再打扰你了
Where is Yaoyao?
瑶瑶在哪里？
How did that happen?
那是怎么发生的？
I didn't see her
我没有见到她
she betrayed you
她背叛了你
It's not worth worrying about her
不值得为她担心
She also has unavoidable difficulties.
她也有无法回避的困难。
The fog that night
那晚的雾
Threaten her family
威胁她的家人
when i soak in the sea
当我泡在海里的时候
i want to know everything
我想了解一切
Night fog man
夜雾人
You doubted me from the beginning
从一开始就怀疑我
They asked me to steal data
他们让我窃取数据
come try me
来试试我
They are already sunny
他们已经阳光明媚了
Still using me
还在利用我
come try me
来试试我
I am not Yaoyao who was sold.
我不是被卖的瑶瑶。
She bugged you.
她对你进行了窃听
I'll also take you to the fishing boat.
我也带你去钓鱼船。
Yes
是的
I think she threatened people.
我认为她威胁了人们。
That wasn't her intention
那不是她的意图
There's no need to run away for her
没必要为了她逃跑
whether forced or not
无论被迫与否
she is a spy
她是一名间谍
take a look
看一看
She knows both of us
她认识我们俩
been touched
接触过
perhaps
大概
but she didn't say
但她没有说
Night fog man
夜雾人
What does it mean
这是什么意思
She said she wanted to go ashore
她说她想上岸
But no chance
但没有机会了
she is the last
她是最后一个
What did you say to me?
你对我说什么了？
if i am early
如果我早
i should tell her
我应该告诉她
Huang Zicheng
黄子诚
Ask me clearly
你问我清楚
this is not a game
这不是一个游戏
Not so much
没那么多
I know
我知道
I won't run away for her
我不会为了她而逃跑
I just want to tell you
我只想告诉你
she's not completely corrupt
她并没有完全腐败
she still has hope
她仍然有希望
if there is a chance
如果有机会的话
See if you can.
看看你能不能。
save her
救救她
This is a brutal killing
这是一场残酷的杀戮
instead of saving fallen souls
而不是拯救堕落的灵魂
do you understand
你明白吗
knew
知道了
If she still has hope in her heart
如果她心里还有希望
She will teach with her actions
她会用她的行动来教导
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
you can exit
你可以退出
end
结尾
When you are done with me I will throw me away
当你们用完我之后我就会把我扔掉
I won't abandon you
我不会抛弃你
The spy abandoned you
间谍抛弃了你
you have landed
你已经着陆了
later action
稍后的行动
you don't need to join
你不需要加入
But before the event is over
但在事件结束之前
Be careful
当心
if they contact you
如果他们联系你
contact me anytime
随时联系我
The game is?
游戏是？
Should I continue?
我还继续吗
let go
松手
If I need you I will go to you
如果我需要你我会去找你
It doesn't matter
没关系
For you
为你
Just go back to the beginning
只要回到最初
Now
现在
I'm not the same anymore
我不再一样了
I'll send you the address
我把地址发给你
see you later.
待会儿见。
OK
好的
This is a secret base
这是一个秘密基地
Qin area
秦地区
Sorry Wu Xi
对不起吴曦
we give you
我们给你
I hid this
我隐藏了这个
It seemed like I was the only one surrounded by the sound of drums
似乎只有我一个人被鼓声包围
sit down
坐下
you are part of the plan
你是计划的一部分
your plan is
你的计划是
since when
从何时起
I discovered Yaoyao
我发现了瑶瑶
I began to doubt Huang Zichen's identity.
我开始怀疑黄子晨的身份。
Do you remember Yaoyao?
你还记得瑶瑶吗？
Can you treat me to dinner?
你能请我吃饭吗？
when she just came back from thailand
当她刚从泰国回来时
meal time
吃饭时间
I found the details
我发现了细节
Your phone case is nice.
你的手机壳不错。
Yao Yao sent
姚姚 发送
She suddenly gave Huang Zichen a gift.
她突然给黄子晨送了一份礼物。
1 mobile phone case
1个手机壳
I have a little doubt
我有一点疑问
I'll check it out
我去检查一下
There's a bug inside
里面有一个窃听器
At that moment I was convinced
那一刻我确信
Huang Zichen’s identity
黄子晨的身份
has been exposed
已经被曝光了
Sooner or later he will take action against Huang Zichen.
迟早他会对黄子辰出手。
so do something
所以做点什么
give them a goal
给他们一个目标
forwarded to you
转给你
Yes
是的
I did it on purpose
我是故意的
Secrets from the National Security Agency
来自国家安全局的秘密
secretly
偷偷
Help Huang Zicheng's virtual image
帮助黄子成的虚拟形象
Just at this time
就在这个时候
Shoichi caused the accident.
翔一引发了事故。
Then Yogiri started trying.
然后 Yogiri 开始尝试。
He has
他有
Huang Zicheng came to threaten me.
黄子成来威胁我。
Let's kill Shoichi.
咱们杀了翔一吧。
Was it your hand?
是你动的手吗？
No
不
I propose to Yogiri
我向约吉里求婚
I need help
我需要帮助
on this occasion
在这种场合
You can pull this boss out
你可以把这个老板拉出来
but i never thought
但我从没想过
He asked Yaoyao to act.
他让瑶瑶演戏。
So you took advantage of Yaoyao
所以你占了瑶瑶的便宜
Yes
是的
people in morgue
太平间里的人
Probably not Soo Yi
应该不是秀伊
certainly
当然
body bag zipper
裹尸袋拉链
Did you do any tricks?
你做过什么把戏吗
they are difficult to open
它们很难打开
Don't let people find out
不让人们发现
Do you think Mr. Zhang will go?
你觉得张先生会去吗？
she doesn't believe me
她不相信我
She will definitely go
她一定会去
The show is for them
表演是为他们准备的
Very important
很重要
Your plan is so detailed
你的计划是如此详细
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
你为什么不早点告诉我？
because you are right
因为你是对的
Suspects about Sauer's death
绍尔死亡疑点
It's also part of our plan
也是我们计划的一部分
everything went smoothly
一切进行得都很顺利
Even people who look at me are suspicious.
连看着我的人都会怀疑。
your concerns
你的疑虑
Just hiding my danger
只是隐藏了我的危险
even if you tell me
即使你告诉我
I will also cooperate
我也会配合
The fog from the previous night shrouded Yaoyao.
前一晚的迷雾笼罩着瑶瑶。
A listening device was installed
安装了窃听装置
I have no idea
我不知道
Is there eyeliner around me?
我周围有眼线吗？
I did not notice
我没有注意到
that's why i decided
这就是为什么我决定
this drama
这部剧
the truth
真相
I agree
我同意
Your stations are connected to each other
你们的电台相互连接
If there is even the slightest omission
如果有哪怕一点点的遗漏
i will lose everything
我会失去一切
that's why
这就是为什么
Must be careful
必须小心谨慎
Wuxi
无锡
You are now officially joining
您现在正式加入
Become a Fisherman Project Member
成为渔夫计划成员
forest plan
行林计划
here we go
开始了
Current Director of the Fisherman Project
现任渔夫计划总负责人
We are not in the Tianjin Hai Bureau.
我们不是在津海局。
in the security department
在安全部
You look like Director Zhao.
你看起来像赵主任。
and other engineers
还有其他工程师
Everything is borrowed from the ministries.
一切都是各部借来的。
with the two people in front of you
和你面前的两个人
all ministries
所有部委
The detective who was transferred
被调来的侦探
This special operations group
这个特别行动组
behind the scenes
幕后
support this action
支持这个行动
Fisherman's plan goals
渔夫计划的目标
What
什么
Xinglin behavior
行琳行为
this is a huge plan
这是一个巨大的计划
The first step is to look up at the sun
第一步是抬头看太阳
Win Mr. Zhang’s trust
赢得张总的信任
through her
通过她
Tsui's spy network
津井的间谍网络
eradicate
铲除
since it was discovered
自从被发现之后
Mr. Zhang
张先生
Why can't we catch it directly?
为什么不能直接抓到呢？
because
因为
This Mr. Zhang is playing a game.
这位张先生正在玩游戏。
There is another one online
网上还有一个
in spy games
在间谍游戏中
Yes
是的
She and this person
她和这个人
Please contact me only during games
请仅在游戏期间联系我
This person's name is Z
这个人的名字叫Z
He is in control
他掌控在自己手中
of all industries
所有行业的
User repository
用户存储库
As long as Mr. Zhang is here
只要张先生在
what kind of person do you need
你需要什么样的人
tell him
告诉他
He can give you some goals
他可以给你一些目标
and their materials
和他们的材料
Who is Z?
那Z是谁？
we don't even know
我们甚至不知道
Maybe Mr. Zhang
也许是张先生
I don't know who it is
我不知道是谁
and
而且
Mr. Zhang holds it in his hand.
张先生手里拿着它。
Another trump card
又一张王牌
Hidden within biota
隐藏在生物群内
before us
在我们之前
I always thought it was Huang Zichen
我一直以为是黄子晨
This is their trump card
这是他们的王牌
at this point
在此刻
He is just a tool
他只是一个工具
Is the news reliable?
消息可靠吗？
Sauce
酱
A man was abandoned in the night fog
一个人被遗弃在夜雾里
Shore wakes up
肖尔醒来了
Wuxi
无锡
You were involved in this operation
你参与了这次行动
The goal is to find it
目标是找到它
in game
在游戏里
I can understand one thing
我能明白一件事
User materials for various industries
各行业的用户材料
database user
数据库用户
Z
Z
give it to me
交给我
Tianyang
天陽
You continue to contact Mr. Zhang.
你继续联系张总。
Find all her offline status
找到她所有的离线状态
Especially hidden things
尤其是隐藏的东西
within biological group
生物组内
That trump card
那张王牌
make out
认出
feels good
感觉很好
This answered my heart
这回答了我的心
big problem
大问题
Yogiri is on a secret service mission.
约吉里正在执行特工任务。
what is developing
正在发展什么
The origins of gamers
游戏玩家的起源
High probability
概率高
This is Mr. Z
这是Z先生
You can provide a repository like this
您可以提供这样的存储库
Most likely a major site
很可能是一个主要网站
of these users
这些用户的
Work and life information
工作、生活信息
Yes
是的
But there are many such websites
不过这样的网站还有很多
Find players we know
寻找我们认识的球员
Find out what they signed up for
了解他们注册了什么
Applicable websites
适用网站
I think you'll find it soon
我想你很快就会找到它
able
能
I have a hunch
我有种预感
this clue
这条线索
may help us
可能会帮助我们
Basically
从根本上
Eliminate spy games in one go
一次性消灭间谍游戏
that's optimistic
这很乐观
Of course that is
当然那是
I'm not you
我不是你
everything
一切
I only want bad things
我只想坏事
I was doing this so deeply by myself all day long.
我一整天都一个人如此深入地做这件事。
but you know
但你知道
I still praise you
我还是夸你
Planning is tightly cyclical.
计划是紧密循环的。
Protect Huang Zicheng
保护黄子成
I brought Principal Zhang out.
我把张校长带出来了。
I also earned her trust in you.
我也赢得了她对你的信任。
Even if you say so, I'm amazing.
即使你这么说，我也很了不起。
this is a bit disappointing
这有点令人失望
if she wasn't alone
如果她不孤单的话
spy story
间谍故事
you two are
你们两个是
this is perfect for you
这非常适合你
I approached her
我走近她
Because I think she's suspicious.
因为我觉得她很可疑。
hope so
希望如此
this is not the end
这不是结束
What are you going to do now?
你现在打算做什么？
You're not done yet.
你还没有完成。
The ones I mentioned are Huang Zicheng and Yao Yao.
我提到的就是黄子成和姚姚。
Yaoyao didn't touch her first.
瑶瑶先没有动她。
She is my best support
她是我最好的支持
Huang Zicheng
黄子诚
I've sent him out
我已经把他送出去了
you replaced
你替换了
Huang Zicheng’s location
黄子成的位置
He and Yaoyao
他和瑶瑶
divided into
分为
Can it be divided?
可以分吗？
Even if you can't split it, you still get points.
即使你无法分割它，你仍然可以获得积分。
now in his mind
现在在他心里
That must be sad
那一定是悲伤的
You said this person really doesn't talk.
你说这个人真不说话。
I'm driving.
我正在开车。
what are you saying
你在说什么
Just believe me
只要相信我
feeling abandoned
被抛弃的感觉
don't comfort him
不要安慰他
no need
没有必要
bad
糟糕的
The mission went smoothly
任务进行得很顺利
I didn't misunderstand you
我没有误解你
That promise is
那个承诺是
Turn it into cash quickly
赶快把它变成现金
certainly
当然
Your sister can leave at any time
你姐姐可以随时离开
promise
承诺
OK
好的
I?
我？
is that so
是这样吗
I can leave Jinhai.
我能够离开津海了。
You are in Jinhai
你在津海
I have other responsibilities
我还有其他职责
The purpose of dragging Huang Zichen into the water
拉黄子晨下水的目的
Just to control Huang Jiaming.
就是为了控制黄家明。
Now Huang Zicheng
現在黄子誠
It’s no longer valuable
已经不值钱了
The scorching sun is also coming for you
烈日高照也为你而来
draw water
汲水
Leave me in Jinhai
把我留在津海
Useless
没有用
How could you leave in such a hurry?
你怎么可以这么匆忙离开？
i killed someone
我杀了人
It's too dangerous to stay here
留在这里太危险了
It's safe to return to headquarters.
可以安全返回总部了。
you do not need to worry
你不用担心
Jinjing now
现在的津井
your best place
你最好的地方
Why
为什么
Gao Tianyang has arrived at Jinhai.
高天阳已经到了津海。
mobile umbrella
移动伞
as long as you need
只要你需要
he will help you work
他会帮助你工作
come back now
现在回来
Such a relationship is a waste
这样的关系就是一种浪费
but i still
但我还是
What tasks will you perform?
您将执行什么任务？
The organization has plans
该组织有计划
when i
我什么时候
to complete the task
来完成任务
hope
希望
I can do it forever
我可以做到永远
You still here
你还在
I want to be with Huang Zichen
我想和黄子晨在一起
You are me and him
你就是我和他
Is it okay?
还可以吗？
if he knows you
如果他认识你
Kill for him
为他杀人
terribly sorry
很抱歉
but you already are
但你已经是
I promise to heaven
我向高天许诺
you promised heaven
你曾许诺过天堂
I won't use yellow anymore.
我不会再用黄子成了。
I don't use him
我不使用他
You still here
你还在
Face things you can't control
面对那些你无法控制的事情
You must learn to accept
你必须学会​​接受
enjoy
享受
OK
好的
But I have one more thing to do.
但我还有一件事要做。
I don't want any more interceptions
我不想再有任何拦截
continue
继续
no problem
没问题
I believe you now.
我现在相信你了。
You sent me home suddenly
你突然送我回家
what happened
发生了什么
elder sister
姐姐
I've been doing this for a while
这件事我已经做了一段时间了
I can't explain it to you either.
我也无法给你解释清楚。
I can only tell you
我只能告诉你
being threatened
受到威胁
They threaten me with your safety
他们用你的安全威胁我
threaten
威胁
Who are you?
你是谁？
Did you report the crime to the police?
你向警方报案了吗？
I have no choice
我别无选择
i will tell you everything
我会告诉你一切
The police can't control this
警察也无法控制这些
just if
只是如果
You have been in the United States.
你一直在美国。
they will continue to threaten me
他们将继续威胁我
Trying to blackmail me into doing something
试图敲诈我做某事
what i don't want to do
我不想做什么
But my current job is
但我现在的工作是
Will you listen to me this time?
这次你愿意听我说吗？
You can look for it again after you get back from get off work.
下班回来后可以再找找。
I just want to
我现在只想
Both of us
我们俩
peace, security
和平、安全
living together
住在一起
I can
我可以
OK
好的
i listen to you
我听你
We look forward to your return.
我们期待您的归来。
What we know so far
我们目前所知道的
game player
游戏玩家
All users browsing the site
所有浏览网站的用户
of which pure
其中纯
Shi Lei
石磊
Zhu Yan
朱言
sunny
阳光明媚
All from the Tetsuzo website
全部来自Tetsuzo网站
Deep users
深度用户
Read aloud
大声朗读
Yes
是的
I'm currently learning about
我目前正在了解
Client work information
客户工作信息
Hobby website
爱好网站
Not so much
没那么多
But Tetsuya is one of them.
但哲也就是其中之一。
So far we have not disclosed
到目前为止我们还没有透露
one question
一个问题
Agent task selection mechanism
Agent任务选择机制
What should I do if it’s foggy at night?
晚上有雾怎么办？
among a huge user base
在庞大的用户群体中
Choose the one that is most useful to them
选择对他们最有用的一项
excellent player
优秀球员
and pull them into the water
并将它们拉入水中
Read aloud
大声朗读
Currently domestic
目前国内
The most professional influence
最具专业影响力
Q&A session
问答现场
it contains many things
它包含很多东西
Professional positions
专业岗位
People who like to visit this site
喜欢访问该网站的人
academically
学术上
There is a certain threshold
有一定的门槛
some of them
他们中有一些
contains a lot
包含很多
people who work confidentially
从事保密工作的人
Like Shi Lei
像石磊
Zhu Yan
朱言
sunny
阳光明媚
or participate in
或参与
Major-related students
专业相关学生
just like dad
就像爸爸一样
Yes
是的
target audience
目标听众
Covered up spies
掩盖了间谍
a group of people you want to attract
一群你想吸引的人
If the night fog comes
如果夜雾袭来
User information by industry
按行业分类的用户信息
can be easily pulled
可以轻松拉动
desired goal
期望的目标
later
稍后
make believe
让我相信
Philosophical reading and spy games
哲学阅读和间谍游戏
I'm sure there's a connection
我确信有联系
Yao Yao
姚瑶
Yes
是的
Yaoyao is a philosopher.
瑶瑶是一位哲学家。
This may not be a coincidence
这可能不是巧合
Your guess is
你的猜测是
convincing
有说服力的
but
但
Again, there is not enough evidence to support this
再次强调，没有足够的证据支持这一点
right now we
我们现在
We still need to break through
我们还需要突破
I think Yaoyao knows.
我想瑶瑶是知道的。
Is there a relationship between reading philosophy and games?
阅读哲学和游戏有关系吗？
she shouldn't know
她不应该知道
I think
我觉得
Mr. Z in the game
游戏中的Z先生
hidden in philosophy
隐藏在哲学里
if we can find him
如果我们能找到他
this is the best
这是最好的
Thanks.
谢谢。
Please give me a glass of the same thing.
请给我一杯同样的东西。
OK
好的
How long have we not seen each other?
我们多久没见面了
1 week
1周
haven't seen you for a long time
好久不见
After disembarking
下船後
what have you done
你做了什么
i know everything
我知道所有的东西
Little Tianyou taught me
小天佑教我的
Pull the Kokuan people into the water
把Kokuan的人拉到水里
You know
你知道的
Is this serious?
这件事严重吗？
I know
我知道
but i have to do it
但我必须这么做
you really don't need
你真的不需要
come and save me
来救我
so
这样
yourself
你自己
looks important
看起来很重要
The person who wants to save you is Gao Tianyang.
要救你的人是高天阳。
Yogiri takes advantage of this.
Yogiri 利用了这一点。
I am originally a night fog person.
我本来就是一个夜雾人。
This is the mission they gave me.
这就是他们赋予我的使命。
Task# Task#
任务# 任务#
I can't even say
我什至不能说
this is not your fault
这不是你的错
In the end we both
最后我们俩
get acquainted
结识
but
但
we all cheated on each other
我们都互相欺骗了
but i can't
但我做不到
I will leave you to die alone.
我会留下你一个人去死。
so save you
所以拯救你
in order to complete the mission
为了完成使命
Are you still helping Yogiri do his job?
你还在帮助约吉里做他的工作吗？
Are there any other options?
还有其他选择吗？
practical things
实际的事情
Things are not as bad as you think
事情并没有你想象的那么糟糕
I know you are threatened
我知道你受到威胁
you still have a chance
你还有机会
be a hero
成为英雄
you can't save anything
你无法保存任何东西
you forget
你忘记
avoid these things
避免这些事情
Finally landed
终于落地了
Stop participating
别再参与了
I can
我可以
It's over between us
我们之间结束了
From the moment you step on the plane
从您踏上飞机的那一刻起
It's over now
现在结束了
That's why I'm leaving no stone unturned today
这就是为什么我今天不遗余力
chose this place
选择了这个地方
I was just thinking
我刚在想
where does it start
事情从哪里开始
end somewhere
在某处结束
sounds good
听起来不错
I like this sense of ceremony
喜欢这种仪式感
this looks slick
这看起来很光滑
Do you regret it?
你后悔吗？
what do you regret
你后悔什么
I regret knowing you
我后悔认识你
return
还
sorry for what we went through
对我们所经历的事感到遗憾
Nothing to regret
没什么可后悔的
It's impossible anyway
无论如何都是不可能的
let's try again
让我们再试一次
rather than clinging to it
而不是执着于它
It would be better if you open your eyes a little wider
眼睛再睁大一点就好了
go ahead
前进
we are in this world
我们在这个世界上
everything is just one
一切都只是一个
small dust
小灰尘
Not everyone is that important
不是每个人都那么重要
goodbye.
再见。